(
"ai_sub_version": "1.11.0",
"subtitles_prompt_version": 3,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": "gemini-cli:gemini-3-flash-preview",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true
),
"gemini_cli": (
"timeout": 600
)
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": true,
"fps": 1,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"encoder": "libx264"
)
),
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"subtitles": 8
),
"retry": (
"run": 3,
"max": 9,
"delay": 30
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false
)
hololive presents
Secret Society holoX
La+ Darknesss
Takane Lui
Secret Society holoX
Hakui Koyori
Kazama Iroha
Secret Society holoX
Anniversary Parade
Enjoy the parade!
全世界、激震!
The whole world is shaking!
あの超大作が
That blockbuster movie...
ついに
...is finally...
スクリーンへ!!
...hitting the big screen!!
タイムリミットは24時間
The time limit is 24 hours.
人類の希望は
Humanity's hope is...
4人の「[BEEP]」に託された
...entrusted to four "[BEEP]" members.
なんだ？ここは！？
What is this place!?
どうして...こんなのひどいよ！
Why... This is terrible!
私のことはもういい、先に行け！
Forget about me, just go on ahead!
いろは～～～～！！
Iroha~~~~!!
あ、おふざけんな、お前！
Hey, stop messing around!
待ってよ！
Wait up!
やだー！
No way!
なんでー！
Why!?
私たちの絆は、永遠！
Our bond is eternal!
みんなで人類を救うんだ！！
We're going to save humanity together!!
絶対に忘れないよ......
I'll never forget......
自分史上、最高傑作です
It's my greatest masterpiece ever.
holoX 4周年 サイコー！
holoX 4th Anniversary is the best!
犯人は...この中にいる！
The culprit... is among us!
うえー！？俺！？
Whaaat!? Me!?
「なんかすごいミステリー」第1位
No. 1 in "Some Kind of Amazing Mystery"
これは......
This is......
謎が謎を呼ぶ怒涛の展開
A turbulent development where mystery leads to mystery
背後から刀で一振り......
A single stroke of a sword from behind......
探偵殿、どうしたでござるか？
Detective, what's wrong?
怪しい！
Suspicious!
殺人犯と一緒の場所にいられるか！部屋に戻らせてもらう！
As if I can stay in the same place as a murderer! I'm going back to my room!
怪しい
Suspicious
......ふふふふふ
......Hehehehehe
怪しい
Suspicious
登場人物全員"容疑者"
All characters are "suspects"
最初から最後までハラハラドキドキでしたー
It was thrilling from beginning to end.
holoX 4周年 サイコー！
holoX 4th Anniversary is the best!
私の名前は博衣こより！どこにでもいる普通の高校生！
My name is Hakui Koyori! An ordinary high school student you can find anywhere!
ただ一つ人と違うことは、科学が好き......ってところかな？
The only thing that's different from others is that I love science... I guess?
いっけなーい！遅刻遅刻ーー
Oh no! I'm late, I'm late!
いったー
Ouch...
転校初日から始まるドタバタな日常！？
A slapstick daily life starting from the first day of transfer!?
見つけた
Found you.
一緒にいるとなんか安心するでござる
When I'm with you, I feel somewhat at ease.
いただきますよ、あー！...おのれ、女！
I'm having this, ah! ...Curse you, woman!
個性あふれる4人が紡ぐ甘じょっぱい四角な物語――
A bittersweet square story woven by four unique individuals—
甘じょっぱさが絶妙でしたー！
The bittersweetness was exquisite!
holoX 4周年 サイコー！
holoX 4th Anniversary is the best!
あ、あなた......！holoX 4周年を検索しちゃったんですか！！！
Oh, you...! Did you just search for holoX 4th Anniversary!!!
決して、検索してはイケナイ
Never, search for it.
「#SSholoX4周年」
"#SSholoX4thAnniversary"
holoXを検索した人
The person who searched for holoX
"SSholoX4周年"を検索した人間に降りかかる
Befalls the person who searched for "#SSholoX4thAnniversary"
数々の出来事――
Numerous events—
ルイ姉……
Lui-nee...
いろは、大丈夫だから……
Iroha, it's okay...
いろは？
Iroha?
いろは！？
Iroha!?
ゔぁー！
Baa!
（すごい悲鳴！）
(Screams loudly!)
終始鳥肌が立ちっぱなしでしたー
I had goosebumps the whole time!
せーの
Ready, set...
holoX 4周年サイコー！
holoX 4th Anniversary is the best!
Ladies and gentlemen,
these are the super rookies.
Six!
Let's go!
Lala-patta palala-patta...
迷宮なラビリンス
A Confusing Labyrinth
A confusing labyrinth
の、招かれた招待状
An invited invitation
秘密で秘匿の秘伝マンション
A secret and hidden arcane mansion
彼方此方のドアの向こうに
Beyond every door
No way, no get away
幻想迷走のホークアイ
Hawk-eye of fantasy and straying
迫る白羽はウォークライ
The approaching blade is a war cry
奔走自在に突破口　もんどり打つのさ走馬灯
A free-run breakthrough, somersaulting like a revolving lantern
Xに囚り込まれていくよ
Getting pulled into the X
確信で飾れ！
Adorn it with conviction!
無情 乱れ咲け　断末魔
Ruthless, bloom in disorder, screams of death
怒号 響かせろ　絶叫中
Let the roars echo while screaming
さあ 壊すご用意よ　ピュア
Now, get ready to break, pure
響け　笑い声
Echo, sound of laughter
ふんわり本気
Softly serious
力こそパワー
Power is might
素敵な迷宮のラビリンス
A wonderful confusing labyrinth
せーの
One, two...
迷宮なラビリンス
A confusing labyrinth
ね、羅針盤失くして A-A-A
Losing the compass, A-A-A
恐怖 秒で絶つだわ Wi-Fi
Cutting fear in seconds with Wi-Fi
九重街で最強るーむ　だけど
The strongest room in Kokonoe town, however
身体の回路は普通に　あぶない
The body's circuits are normally dangerous
One shot Vampire
現実 踊るマリオネット
落ちる部屋は脱出(ダツメト)
Reality's dancing marionette
Falling into an escape room
ランク外は関知前　嗚呼落命　赤く鳴れ
Unranked, unconcerned, ah, death, ring out in red
Xに囚り込まれていくよ
Getting pulled into the X
迷える子羊くんたち！
Lost little lambs!
お砂糖 スパイス それとピンクな4周年で
ハイになれるドリンク できたよー！
Sugar, spice, and with a pink 4th anniversary,
I've made a drink that'll get you high!
毒でも飲んでくださいねー
Please drink it even if it's poison!
ホロックス・サキに！
To holoX first!
さあさあ 皆殿 のーべでござる！
Now then, everyone, bottoms up!
我が輩のたー！
My turn!
いや お前が飲むんかーい！
Hey, you're the one drinking it?!
じゃ、とりあえずー
Then, for now...
乾杯！
Cheers!
神霊の回路から　テレポート気味 警報
From the divine spirit circuit, a teleport-like alarm
塗り替えられる常夜　見果てろ
An overwritable eternal night, see it to the end
怒号 響かせろ　絶叫中
Let the roars echo while screaming
さあ 壊すご用意よ　ピュア
Now, prepare to break it, pure
お前たちもな！
You too!
Lala-patta palala-patta...
立ち止まって 5人の鼓動
Stopping and listening to five hearts beating
重なって 声を高らかに
Overlapping, raising our voices high
ラパパ ダラララパパ
Rapapa darara rapapa
星天の 海を越えるため
To cross the starry seas
つまり満天 不敵が似合い
In other words, the full sky and boldness suit us
千夜万花の スーパーフューチャーパーティーラビリンス
Labyrinth of a thousand nights and ten thousand flowers' super future party
バイバイ
Bye-bye
はーい！ イェーイ！
Yay! Cheers!
ということで、
So,
ホロックス4周年！
It's holoX's 4th Anniversary!
おめでとー！
Congratulations!
あーみんな、張り切っていくぞー！
Alright everyone, let's give it our all!
じゃあちょっとね、これからの
Now then, regarding our
活動の抱負を...
aspirations for future activities...
早いね、展開早いね。
That was quick. Fast transition.
私から？
Starting with me?
私から？聞いてないよ、私からなの？どうしようかな。
From me? I wasn't told, it's me? What should I do...
えっと、みんなありがとう。
Um, thank you everyone.
えっとどうしようかな、5年目も...
Um, what should I say... in the 5th year...
頑張るぞ、ホロックス頑張るぞ！
We'll do our best, holoX will do its best!
イェーイ！
Yay!
はい、じゃあこより。
Alright, next is Koyori.
はい！
Yes!
えー、この5年目は4人で、もっと団結力をガッと強めて、
Um, in this 5th year, the four of us will strengthen our unity much more,
そろそろ日本征服ぐらいはしていきたいなと。
and I want to start moving towards something like conquering Japan.
確かにね。
True, true.
5年目の区切りのいいところにね。
At a good milestone like the 5th year.
世界はまだちょっと難しいけど、
Conquering the world is still a bit hard, but...
日本征服頑張ります！
We'll do our best to conquer Japan!
はい、いろはー。
Next, Iroha.
はい！皆さん、
Yes! Everyone,
ご、ご、ござるの5！
Go, go, Gozaru's 5!
ということで、5年目もね、元気に健やかに健康に
So, in the 5th year, energetically and healthily,
活動頑張っていきたいとおもいます！ホロックス5周年...
I want to do my best in our activities! holoX 5th anniversary...
5年目頑張るぞ！
5th year, let's do our best!
はい、じゃあ私いいですか？
Okay, may I go next?
今年も生き残るぞ！
I'll survive this year too!
生き残るね、毎年同じこと言ってるよね。
Survive, huh. You say that every year.
でも生き残れた、今年も。
But you did survive this year too.
そして！
And!
来年こそ、5年目こそ、我々の年にするぞ！
Next year, the 5th year, we'll make it our year!
おー！イェーイ！
Oh! Yay!
ちょっとダサい、待ってダサい。
That's a bit uncool. Wait, way too uncool.
なんで、なんで、同じことやってるのに。
Why? We're all doing the same thing.
ちょっとみんな見てくださいよ。
Everyone, please take a look.
ライブステージすごい！
The live stage is amazing!
ホロックスの最初の登場からさ、うちらカッコよかったでしょ。
Since the very first intro of holoX, we looked cool, right?
カッコよかったでしょ！カッコよかった。
We did! We looked cool.
しかも、このステージ、ただ広いだけじゃなくて、
What's more, this stage isn't just wide,
色んな仕掛けがありますので。
it has various gimmicks.
注目して、なんかね出てきたりとか。
Keep an eye out, things like coming out...
出てきたり、出てきたり。
Coming out, coming out.
そして、上がったりとか。
And going up, and so on.
尻尾が上がってるぞ。
The tail is going up!
変形したりとかさ、
Like transforming,
合体とか！
or combining!
合体はさすがに無理だろ。
Combining is definitely impossible.
合体したい！
I want to combine!
合体はしたかったんですけど、
I wanted to combine, but...
ちょっとさすがにホロックス予算が少なく...
holoX's budget is unfortunately a bit low...
当たり前じゃないですか、こよりさんにいくらかけてると思ってるんですか。
Well, obviously. How much do you think we're spending on you, Koyori?
ちょっと5人の給料もっと上げてくれてもいいよね。
Hey, you could raise our salaries a bit more.
でもこのステージできたからいいじゃん。
But we got this stage, so it's fine, right?
確かにね、ありがとう。
True, thank you.
ということで、5年目もホロックスファンの皆さん、
So, to all the holoX fans in our 5th year,
こんな我々ですけどよろしくお願いします。
please continue to support us as we are.
ちなみにここでお知らせでございます。
By the way, here's an announcement.
お知らせ！
Announcement!
ホロライブ公式チャンネルのメンバーシップに入ると、
If you join the Hololive official channel membership,
秘密結社holoX 4周年記念！！
公式メンバーシップ 限定絵文字・限定壁紙
12月1日の配信で使える！もらえる！
Secret Society holoX 4th Anniversary!!
Official Membership Limited Emoji & Limited Wallpapers
Use them and get them in the Dec 1st stream!
なんと限定絵文字スタンプが使えるようになりますので、ぜひコメントで使って盛り上げてください。
you'll be able to use limited emoji stamps, so please use them in the comments to hype things up.
さらに！なんと今日からもう一つメンバーシップ特典があるらしいんですけども、
Furthermore! Apparently there's another membership benefit starting today,
先日発表した新曲『スキデカ』と『プライベートアイズ』の壁紙ももらえちゃいます！
you can also get wallpapers for the recently announced new songs "Sukideka" and "Private Eyes"!
めっちゃいいじゃん！俺たちも入らなきゃいけないのかも。
That's awesome! Maybe we should join too.
はい！
Yes!
そして本日は、何やらライブだけではなく...
And today, it's not just about the live performance...
重要な情報が...
But there's also some important info...
盛り、盛り、盛り、盛りだくさんらしいので！
A whole, whole, whole, whole lot of it, it seems!
盛りだくさん！盛りだくさん！
A whole lot! A whole lot!
皆さん、最後までちゃんと見ていくように！
Everyone, make sure you watch until the very end!
途中離席禁止です！よろしくお願いします！
Leaving midway is forbidden! We're counting on you!
盛り、盛り、盛りだくさん。
Lots and lots of info.
森の字を作って...
Making the character for "Mori"...
やめなさい！ちょっと、三人で混ぜるなよ！
Stop that! Hey, don't mix the three of us together!
ちょっと待ってください、なんですか？
Wait a minute, what's going on?
もう早くしないと！
We've got to hurry up!
みんなに見せられないから、ライブ！
Or we won't be able to show the live to everyone!
はい、早速、最初は...
Alright, without further ado, first is...
ドコドコドコドコ...
Drumroll...
ジャン！はい！こよりちゃんのパートから！
Ta-da! Alright! Starting with Koyori-chan's part!
イェーイ！
Yay!
何だそのポーズ？
What's with that pose?
ぜひ見てください！可愛い！
Please check it out! So cute!
あ、可愛いね。こより行ってきまーす！
Ah, it is cute. Koyori's heading off now!
いってらっしゃい！
Have a good one!
頑張るぞー！見ててねー！
I'll do my best! Watch me!
見てるよー！頑張れ！
We're watching! Good luck!
走って！ほら、そこ広いから。
Run! Look, there's plenty of space there.
急かさないでー！
Don't rush me!
あ、邪魔だから行くよ。あ、え？俺たちも？
Ah, we're in the way so let's go. Oh, what? Us too?
早く、早く！早くして！
Hurry, hurry! Hurry up!
行くぞ、行くぞ、早く！
Let's go, let's go, quickly!
爆ラブ＋ケミストリー
Bakuretsu Love + Chemistry
作詞・作曲・編曲：ナユタン星人
Lyrics, Composition, Arrangement: Nayutalien
ラブ沸き発散
Love bubbling over and radiating
存在自体マジ神
Your very existence is truly divine
調合は未完成
The mixture is still incomplete
トキメキのケミカル
A chemistry of excitement
おっ！なるほど
Oh! I see
そんじゃこれならどうかと
Well then, how about this?
二進法　ならばラブアトミック
Binary code, then a Love Atomic
ハイ！泡立つこの感情
Yes! This bubbling emotion
混ぜるほどには甘くなるなる
The more you mix, the sweeter it gets
ハイ！ 集中！　過剰のモーション
Yes! Focus! Excessive motion
奇跡的に美味しくなれ
Become miraculously delicious
フラスコにハート　やべ！ラテアート？
Heart in the flask, oh no! Latte art?
効果は絶大　君が一番
The effect is tremendous, you are number one
コー・ラブ・ボ　君になれ
Co-love-bo, become one with you
ちょっと危険な混ぜ混ぜ
A slightly dangerous mix-mix
ドッカン！　ケミストリーなう
Boom! Chemistry now
曖昧な君クロマトグラフィー
Ambiguous you, chromatography
変は恋のジェネリック
Change is the generic of love
もっと夢中になれななな
Get more absorbed, na-na-na
最・低・限　僕のすべて
At the very minimum, all of me
ギュッて留めたい君の胸
I want to hold your heart tight
本能的進歩　フラッシュ・オン
Instinctive progress, Flash On
爆散君とケミストリー
Exploding with you and chemistry
魅惑の甘いエージェント
An alluring sweet agent
溶けるくらいドキドキするはず
Should make your heart throb until it melts
迷信の煙　ハイ！出た！
Smoke of superstition, yes! There it is!
そっちのタイプのドキドキじゃない
Not that kind of heart throb
けどまあ　ある意味成功かな？
But well, is it a success in a way?
ラブ圧上昇　一気にモテなす感
Love pressure rising, feeling popular all at once
調合は試作中
The mixture is still in prototype
感情は飛び散った
My emotions have scattered
お！どこ行く？
Oh! Where are you going?
そんなトライ実験
Such a trial experiment
爆弾を君と重ねてく
I'm overlapping the bomb with you
キュンと目覚めさせたくて
I want to wake you up with a squeeze
ネオパージ
Neo Purge
ラブ夢見る君が一番
You who dreams of love are number one
通・常・開・放　ですか？
Is it a regular opening?
爆裂気味のアンチドート
A somewhat explosive antidote
ドッカン！　ケミストリーなう
Boom! Chemistry now
曖昧な君クロマトグラフィー
Ambiguous you, chromatography
変は恋のジェネリック
Change is the generic of love
どんな色かも観測してさ
Observe what color it is too
ドッカン！　君＋ハート
Boom! You + Heart
溶け出してサジェスト・イマジン
Melting out, Suggest Imagine
君こそが愛のアトミック
You are the very atomic of love
もっと夢中になれななな
Get more absorbed, na-na-na
最・低・限　僕のすべて
At the very minimum, all of me
ギュッて留めたい君の胸
I want to hold your heart tight
本能的進歩　フラッシュ・オン
Instinctive progress, Flash On
爆烈君と追試検証
Exploding with you and re-test verification
最・低・限　僕のすべて
At the very minimum, all of me
ギュッとして僕の胸
Hold my heart tight
本能的進歩　フラッシュ・オン
Instinctive progress, Flash On
爆烈君とケミストリー
Exploding with you and chemistry
次回は君とエターナリー
Next time is eternally with you
興味ないよ
I'm Not Interested
作詞・作曲・編曲：jon-YAKITORY
Lyrics, Composition, Arrangement: jon-YAKITORY
君が好きってこの感情に
By this feeling that I love you...
潰されてる
I'm being crushed
足りないのはどちらの方か
Which one of us is lacking more?
どうでもいいか
Maybe it doesn't even matter
傷ついたって知らないよね
You don't care if I get hurt, do you?
責任逃れ
Evading responsibility
「私を何で好きなんだって」
Asking me, "Why do you like me?"
問い出す流れ
Is just the flow of our conversation
最低な私、
I'm the worst,
あの子の方がいいんだもんね
that girl is better for you, right?
私興味ないよ、君なんて
I'm not interested in someone like you
マジ半端ないね、舐めた真似
Seriously, you're unbelievable, acting so cocky
僕的宇宙なこの愛に
In this love of mine, a personal universe,
壊されないで、愛
Don't be broken, my love
止めどないよ 君の愛を 独り占めしたい
It's unstoppable, I want your love all to myself
特異だろうが何だろうが 抱きしめてあげたい
Whether it's strange or whatever, I want to hold you tight
ライセンス契約 独占のポリラブ
A license agreement for an exclusive poly-love
逃がさない、ずっと
I won't let you get away, ever
君が好きって この感情に
The feeling of "I like you"—
騙されてる
I'm being deceived by it
大事な方は君か私か
Whether you or I am more important,
決めかねてる
I can't decide
甘すぎる君を
You, who are just too sweet
私興味ないよ、君なんて
I'm not interested in someone like you
ほら振り回して、好きなだけ
See? Toy with me as much as you like
僕的宇宙なこの愛を
Because I won't hand over this love of mine,
渡さないから
a personal universe
馬鹿だよね、色ボケだね
You're a fool, blinded by love
それ見たことか、ダサすぎか
See? I told you so. Or are you just too uncool?
もう他でもない、あなたに呪われたまま
It's none other than you who has cursed me like this
私興味ないよ、君なんて
I'm not interested in someone like you
馬鹿なふりして、あげただけ
I was only pretending to be a fool for you
愛と愛をぶつけ合って
Clashing our loves against each other
ぐちゃぐちゃになって
Becoming a complete mess
私興味ないよ、君なんて
I'm not interested in someone like you
マジ半端ないね、舐めた真似
Seriously, you're unbelievable, acting so cocky
僕的宇宙なこの愛に
In this love of mine, a personal universe,
壊されないで、愛
Don't be broken, my love
見た目だけで終わらせない
Don't just judge me by my appearance
私のこと「可愛い」だけと
You don't just think I'm "cute,"
まさか思っていないよね
do you?
私のホント知っていてほしい
I want you to know the real me
ホントノワタシ
The Real Me
予測誤差の範囲内
Within the margin of prediction error
不測事態も動じない
Unshaken even by unexpected situations
オスマシ顔でいるけど
I keep a composed face, but...
心は常に蒼白く燃え
My heart is always burning with a pale blue flame
諦めはしない 媚びたりもしない
I won't give up, I won't flatter anyone
私、負けない
I will not lose
扱いやっかい奴等の伴
A friend to those hard-to-handle guys
甘く見ると 痛い目見るぞ
Underestimate me and you'll regret it
それでも時に逃げ出してしまいたい
Still, sometimes I just want to run away
そんな衝動に
Caught in that impulse,
弱音吐き出したくなる夜もある
there are nights I want to whine
ほんの小さな 小さな妥協が
Just a tiny, tiny compromise
積み重なり 重なって 動けない
Piles up and up until I can't move
大きな大きな可能性を背負い
Carrying big, big possibilities
未来を狭めてしまうから
might narrow my future
どんなに苦しくても 辛くても
No matter how painful or hard it gets,
後悔だけはしない
I won't have any regrets
往き方の模範じゃなくて
It's not a model of how to go,
「生き方」なんだ
it's my "way of life"
現実と理想の距離を縮められたとしても
Even if the distance between reality and ideals could be closed
オスマシ顔でいるだけ
I'll just keep a composed face,
何事もなかったかのように
as if nothing happened
立ち止まりはしない
I won't stop,
後戻りもしない
I won't turn back,
夢も捨てない
and I won't throw away my dreams
「…ない」とは決めつけないで 全部が私
Don't just decide that I "can't"... all of it is me.
それでも
Even so,
時には ぬくもりが恋しい
sometimes I miss the warmth.
そんな感情に
There are nights when
流されてしまう夜もある
I get swept away by those feelings.
こんな甘い甘い
It's not a weakness
言葉だけ求めてしまうような弱さじゃない
like just seeking sweet, sweet words.
一回二回
Because even experiencing it
経験だって 私を強くしてくれたから
once or twice has made me stronger.
これが これが私の
This is, this is my
ホント
true self.
とても狭い狭い
I'll reach out from within
世界の中から手を出して笑うんだ
this very narrow world and laugh.
広い広い
Because I'm going to run all the way
世界の果てまで 駆け抜けて生きていくんだから
to the end of this wide world.
どんなに濁って 汚れてたって
No matter how muddy or dirty it gets,
楽しんでやるさ
I'll enjoy it.
イケてる私
My cool self
めちゃくちゃじゃなくて 生き方なんだから
isn't a mess, it's just my way of life.
アナスタシスガール feat. ラプラス・ダークネス
Anastasis Girl feat. La+ Darknesss
はーい、注目！
Hey, pay attention!
あれも これも それも
This, that, and that are all
タブー
taboo.
分かってんの？
Do you get it?
分かってちょうだい
Please understand.
ノンストップ・パス・カチャカチャカチャ
Non-stop pass, click-clack-click,
邪魔せんといて
don't get in the way.
分かってんの？
Do you get it?
寄っといでらっしゃい
Come on over.
肥大がベスト 傲慢キャパシティ
Enlargement is best, arrogant capacity,
ペティ・マジェスティ
petty majesty,
死ぬまで上げろぜクリンチ
raise it until death, clinch.
表面だけを
Even if you only grasp
愛嬌把握してもね
the charm on the surface...
痛いの 痛いの
It hurts, it hurts,
飛んでけないくらい
so much it won't fly away.
賞賛悪魔細胞で
With praise demon cells,
脳内いたか爪出し合いましょう
let's bring out the claws inside our brains.
アタシ、
Me,
アナスタシスガール
Anastasis Girl,
不滅強さがディゲール
undying strength is Digel.
だから
So
nana...
一二の三で dandandan
one, two, three and dandandan.
アナスタシスガール
Anastasis Girl,
嫌いしめた罰
the punishment for hating.
君は
You
nana...
地獄へ行け dandandan
go to hell dandandan.
革命ご来！
Revolution is coming!
アナスタシスガーーー
Anastasis Girrrrrl
お口チャック
Zip your mouth,
見なはれ花いちもんめ
look at the Hana-Ichimonme.
お口チャック
Zip your mouth,
アタシだけにサティスファイ
satisfy only me.
すこやかなるときも
Whether in health
やめるときも
or in sickness,
全敗
total defeat,
人間らしくあれ
be human.
ともに
Just because of lack
火花調節不足だけで
of spark adjustment together,
代を
generation...
痛いの 痛いの
If the pain, the pain
飛んでけないなら
won't fly away,
やっチャイ！ 精神論で
Go for it! With spiritualism,
目には目を満たしてやりましょう
let's satisfy an eye for an eye.
アタシ、アナスタシスガール
Me, Anastasis Girl,
プレイコードの時間
time for the play code.
だから
So
nana...
一二の三で dandandan
one, two, three and dandandan.
アナスタシスガール
Anastasis Girl,
極めて遺憾です
it's extremely regrettable.
君は
You
nana...
地獄へ行け dandandan
go to hell dandandan.
革命ご来！
Revolution is coming!
アナスタシスガーーー
Anastasis Girrrrrl
あー
Ah,
ah,
お願い ほっといて
please leave me alone.
あー
Ah,
ah,
お願い ほっといて
please leave me alone.
嘘吐きの代償
The price of a liar,
嘘が飛び散るサティスファクション
satisfaction where lies scatter.
けがれたる生の果てが
The end of a tainted life
生み出したるアンサー
produced the answer.
アタシ、アナスタシスガール
Me, Anastasis Girl,
不滅強さがディゲール
undying strength is Digel.
だから
So
nana...
一二の三で dandandan
one, two, three and dandandan.
アナスタシスガール
Anastasis Girl,
嫌いしめた罰
the punishment for hating.
君は
You
nana...
地獄へ行け dandandan
go to hell dandandan.
革命ご来！
Revolution is coming!
アナスタシスガーーー
Anastasis Girrrrrl
好きじゃない 好きじゃない Ah...
I don't like you, I don't like you, Ah...
スキデカ / ～スキはデカく回顧録～
作詞・作曲・編曲：原口沙輔
Sukideka / ~Big Like Memoir~
Lyrics, Composition, Arrangement: Sasuke Haraguchi
ラブのリポート 冷めあがらぬ感情
A report of love, feelings that won't cool down
バカじゃないの？ 目を覚まして
Are you stupid? Wake up
ねえ 全然平気だし 興味とか関心だらけ
Hey, I'm totally fine, just full of interest and concern
曝け出して ウォンチュ
Expose it, I want you
思考ができなくて困る
I'm in trouble because I can't think
たまに構ってあげる 癖になっちまう
I'll give you some attention occasionally, it'll become a habit
絶妙な距離感 ゲーム 近づく
An exquisite sense of distance, the game is getting closer
一緒でかくてでかくてでかくて
Together, bigger and bigger and bigger
何でも頂戴 最大好き作りましょう
Give me anything, let's create the greatest "like"
それがライクなのかラブなのか
Is that "like" or is it "love"?
はたまた両方なんでは
Or maybe it's both?
ナシ アリ 絶対アリだろ
No? Yes? It's definitely a yes, right?
そしてでかくてでかくてでかくて
And bigger and bigger and bigger
でかくてでかくて
Bigger and bigger
夢は全部叶うからね
Because all dreams will come true
結局重くないと？
In the end, it has to be heavy?
乗らないわ
I won't get on board
交代やっていきましょう
Let's take turns
あなたと好きはでかく好きでかく
With you, "like" is big, "like" is big
しばらくお付き合いよろしくお願いします
Please take care of me for a while
スキ！ デカ！ スキ！ デカ！
Like! Big! Like! Big!
ありがとうございます！
Thank you very much!
たくさんの感情 みんなに伝えて
Convey many emotions to everyone
俺だけにみせてくれたっていいんぜ
It's okay to show it only to me
一人と特別 サービスはできません
I can't provide special service to just one person
それでもいいかな？
Is that okay anyway?
もっと知りたいことだらけ
Just full of things I want to know more about
でも知らない方が幸せか
But is it happier not to know?
絶妙な距離感 ゲーム バランス取り合う
Exquisite sense of distance, a game of balancing each other
一生つかず離れずは辛いから
Being together but apart forever is painful
丁度よく塩梅で
So let's find the right balance
お互いもっと分かり合えたら
If we could understand each other more
特別になれる
We can become special
そうだ！
That's right!
いつも通じ合える
We can always understand each other
この先は想像できないけど
I can't imagine what lies ahead, but
結構いい感じかも
It might be a pretty good feeling
ギリギリでもいいから
Even if it's just barely
そのまま進みます
I'll keep going like this
OK！
OK!
踏みつけていきましょ
Let's trample forward
向上心！
Ambition!
ここで今後の我々について話し合っていきたい
I want to discuss our future here
もういらないでしょ
We don't need that anymore, right?
いいから ほら
Just do it, come on
3 2 1 Let's go!
一緒レッツゴー二人で 俺だって
Let's go together, the two of us, me too
一緒でかくてでかくてでかくて
Together, bigger and bigger and bigger
何でも頂戴 最大好き作りましょう
Give me anything, let's create the greatest "like"
それがライクなのかラブなのか
Is that "like" or is it "love"?
はたまた両方なんでは
Or maybe it's both?
ナシ アリ 絶対アリだろ
No? Yes? It's definitely a yes, right?
そしてでかくてでかくてでかくて
And bigger and bigger and bigger
でかくてでかくて
Bigger and bigger
夢は全部叶うからね
Because all dreams will come true
結局重くないと？
In the end, it has to be heavy?
乗らないわ
I won't get on board
交代やっていきましょう
Let's take turns
一生つかず離れず諦めず
A lifetime of being together and not giving up
丁度よく塩梅で
Finding the right balance
お前ともっとくだらないことでも
Even with sillier things with you
笑っていたい
I want to keep laughing
全力！
Full power!
付き合っていたい
I want to stay with you
この先も変わらない関係性を
A relationship that won't change in the future
ちょっと行き過ぎて
Going a bit too far
またちょっと前進後退
Advancing and retreating a bit again
ひとまず進みます
For now, I'll move forward
OK！
OK!
さぁさぁ戻ります
Now, now, let's go back
なんでだよ
Why though?
好きはでかく好きでかく
"Like" is big, "like" is big
しばらくお付き合いよろしくお願いします
Please take care of me for a while
不思議な関係
A mysterious relationship
お見知りおきを！
Please get to know us!
Private EyeZ
作詞：浦島健太 / 作曲：浦島健太・新Q / 編曲：新Q
Lyrics: Kenta Urashima / Comp.: Kenta Urashima, Shin-Q / Arr.: Shin-Q
超常現象フェノメネス
Supernatural phenomenon, Phenomeness
東奔西走タイムレス
Struggling here and there, Timeless
我ら目指せ この最強座
We aim for this strongest seat
今焼き付けろ
Burn it in now
超常現象フェノメネス
Supernatural phenomenon, Phenomeness
東奔西走タイムレス
Struggling here and there, Timeless
我ら目指せ
We aim
煌めいたって
Even if it glitters
満月の夜 潜り抜けて
Passing through the full moon night
ベールの隙間までため息
A sigh into the gaps of the veil
本能のルーツで探し出して
Find it with the roots of instinct
深い闇へ誘うの
Inviting into the deep darkness
縦横無尽 機密の招待
Running in all directions, a confidential invitation
幽玄の美 世界を制覇
The beauty of the occult, conquering the world
オレンジに染まっていく放課後
After school being dyed in orange
君のために目覚めろ
Awaken for your sake
愛を燃やせ メラメラ
Burn your love, blazing
守り抜くと誓ったあの日から
From that day I swore to protect you
明日のために目覚めろ
Awaken for the sake of tomorrow
炎に飛び乗っちゃえば
If you jump onto the flames
退屈なんてエンドレスさようなら
Endless boredom, goodbye
超常現象フェノメネス
Supernatural phenomenon, Phenomeness
東奔西走タイムレス
Struggling here and there, Timeless
我ら目指せ この最強座
We aim for this strongest seat
今焼き付けろ
Burn it in now
超常現象フェノメネス
Supernatural phenomenon, Phenomeness
東奔西走タイムレス
Struggling here and there, Timeless
我ら目指せ
We aim
煌めいたって
Even if it glitters
栄光目指す 欲望の影を
Aiming for glory, the shadow of desire
忍び足であざむいて
Deceiving with stealthy steps
目の前の手を握りしめよう
Let's grasp the hand in front of us
離れないで
Don't leave
超常現象フェノメネス
Supernatural phenomenon, Phenomeness
東奔西走タイムレス
Struggling here and there, Timeless
我ら目指せ この最強座
We aim for this strongest seat
今焼き付けろ
Burn it in now
超常現象フェノメネス
Supernatural phenomenon, Phenomeness
東奔西走タイムレス
Struggling here and there, Timeless
我ら目指せ
We aim
煌めいたって
Even if it glitters
追い風吹く 欲望の影を
Blowing tailwind, the shadow of desire
忍び足であざむいて
Deceiving with stealthy steps
目の前の手を握りしめよう
Let's grasp the hand in front of us
君と共に
Together with you
止まらないで
Don't stop
このまま
Like this
未来へ
To the future
変化 カムフラージュ 迷彩 カメレオン
Change, camouflage, stealth, chameleon
縦横無尽 飛び込み チョコレート
Free and unconstrained, diving in, chocolate
X or O the power of the kill side
夢のためにメラメラ
Burning bright for the sake of dreams
闇を燃やせメラメラ
Incinerate the darkness, burning bright
どんな時もこの声を届けたい
I want to deliver this voice, no matter when
崖っぷちでメラメラ
Burning bright at the edge of the cliff
諦めるには早いわ
It's too early to give up
恩返し奇跡のおまじない
A magic spell of a miraculous return
真っさらにセクラス 3綺麗な 天然記念
A brand new Secret Society, a beautiful natural monument
想定外の障害だって お真面目
Even with unexpected obstacles, we stay serious
どこにいたって迷子なっちゃってもブンブンデス
No matter where we are, even if we get lost, we're buzzing
有象無象で無理巻いて
Wrapped up in the mundane crowds
電光石火 エスケープ
Lightning-fast escape
君のためにメラメラ
Burning bright for you
愛を燃やせメラメラ
Let love burn bright
守り抜くと誓ったあの日から
Since that day I vowed to protect everything
明日のためにメラメラ
Burning bright for tomorrow
この音に乗せてメラメラ
Riding on this sound, burning bright
退屈なんて無縁でしょ サヨナラ
Boredom has nothing to do with us, goodbye
超常現象 ファンダメンタル
Supernatural phenomenon, fundamental
東奔西走 タイムレプス
Busy running around, time-lapse
オン・ザ・ドット・カー 最高のキャラ
On-the-dot car, the best character
今焼き付けろ
Engrave it in your mind now
超常現象 ファンダメンタル
Supernatural phenomenon, fundamental
東奔西走 タイムレプス
Busy running around, time-lapse
Fundamental! Ambitious!
Ba Ba Ba Bang!
ねーねーねー！ルイ様！めっちゃよかったよね！
Hey hey hey! Rui-sama! That was so good, right?!
めっちゃよかったねー！
It was really good!
楽しかったねー！
It was so fun!
まじかっけー！
Seriously cool!
まだ終わってないから！まだ終わってないよ！
It's not over yet! It's not over!
こっからが最高だよね！
The best part is from here on!
なにこれ？なにこれ？
What's this? What's this?
気づいちゃいました？
Did you notice?
変じゃない？めっちゃかっこいいじゃん！
Isn't it weird? It's super cool!
こよりが作りましたー！
Koyori made it!
また、また経費使ったんかー！
Again, did you use the budget again?!
これがござるの給料８割分？
Is this 80% of Iroha's salary?
いやいやいや、これがあったとしても給料は同じだからね！
No no no, the salary is the same even with this!
なにこれ？
What is this?
ということで、これは告知用カードを...
So, these are announcement cards...
告知ー！
Announcement!
ということで、告知用でグッズ紹介でございますね。
So, it's time to introduce the merchandise.
今回はそういう感じね！
So that's how it is this time!
はい、じゃあ私からね、行きますよ。
Okay, then I'll start.
ホロックス活動... どこ見ればいいか分からない！
HoloX activities... I don't know where to look!
活動4周年記念グッズ「Secret Society holoX Anniversary Parade」、今日の18時より販売開始されております！
4th-anniversary goods 'Secret Society holoX Anniversary Parade' are on sale from 18:00 today!
それではそれぞれ見ていきましょう。まずはプレミアムアクリル色紙、ドン！
Let's look at each one. First, the Premium Acrylic Shikishi!
今回のキービジュアルを使用したアクリル色紙です！
An acrylic shikishi using the key visual for this event!
複製サインとロゴが箔押しになってて、めっちゃいい感じ！
The replica signatures and logo are foil-stamped, it looks great!
そしてお次がこちら、ホロカスリーブ！
And next is this, Holoca Sleeves!
このカードがまさにそれなんですけど、キービジュアルを使用したホロカスリーブです！
This card is exactly it, but it's Holoca sleeves using the key visual!
こちらなんと、60枚入り！
This comes with 60 sheets!
ホロカに使いやすいです！
It's easy to use for Holoca!
はい！アクリルスタンドー！
Next! Acrylic stands!
キービジュアルのデザインの表情違いになってるんで、ぜひアクリル色紙と比べてみてくださいねー！
The expressions are different from the key visual, so please compare them with the shikishi!
気持ち悪い...
That's gross...
そしてこちら、記念メダルも発売しております！
And here, memorial medals are also on sale!
ケースと巾着がついてくる記念メダルでございます。
It's a memorial medal that comes with a case and a drawstring bag.
こちら期生ごとにデザインが異なっておりますので、ホロックスだけのデザインになっております！
The design varies by generation, so it's a unique design just for holoX!
ということで、次はなんのカードかな？カードちゃん！
So, what's the next card? Card-chan!
2枚目オープン！
Open the second one!
タイミーコラボ！
Timee collaboration!
先日タイミーで募集したレアバイトなんですけど、現地の様子があるということで、見ましょう！
Regarding the 'rare part-time job' recruited on Timee recently, we have footage of the scene, let's watch!
すげー！ホロクソー！
Amazing! Holoxers!
ちゃんとホロクソーしてる！
They're properly acting like Holoxers!
あれはあれは、なるように。でもこれを知ってくれた人もいるよね、多分。
That was... what it was. But I'm sure some people learned about us through this.
ね！絶対そう！
Right! Definitely!
もう一枚あります！ドーン！
Here's another one! Boom!
おー！えー！？待って待って、新宿？
Whoa! Eh!? Wait wait, Shinjuku?
あれ後ろにも映ってる。え、聞いてた？
It's on the screen in the background too. Did we hear about this?
あれ聞いてた？あれ聞いてた？ちょっと待って、嘘。
Did you know? Did you know? Wait a sec, no way.
聞いてない！待って、今日のあの21時前に流れていた、あのよくわからない...
We didn't! Wait, that mysterious video that aired before 9 PM tonight...
あのよくわからない。
That mysterious thing.
おい！流れてしまったのかよ！大丈夫か？
Hey! It actually aired!? Is it okay?
あれ？もっとさ、なんかかっこいいMVとかさ、
Huh? If we played a cooler MV or something,
ライブ映像とか流したらもっと...
or live footage, wouldn't it be better...
でもありがとう！ありがとう！やったー！
But thank you! Thank you! Yay!
ということで、こちら、応募どれくらい来たと思う？
So, how many applications do you think we got for this?
300！でもさ、お仕事だからね。
300! But it's work, you know.
お仕事だからやっぱり500人とか来てくれてる？
Since it's work, maybe 500 people applied?
いやでもみんな忙しいから100人とか200人じゃない？
Well, everyone is busy, so maybe 100 or 200?
なんと！
Believe it or not!
数千人の応募が来たということです！
We received applications from several thousand people!
すごすぎる！ありがとう！
That's incredible! Thank you!
驚きすぎやろ！
That's too surprising!
完全に給料もらった体で。給料もらってる時に決まってるだろ。
Definitely acting like people who got paid. Of course they were getting paid.
いろはよりも多めに渡してます。
I'm giving more than I gave to Iroha.
ちょっとやめてよ！
Hey, stop that!
しっかりと福利厚生厚いミーさんですから。
Mee-san has very generous employee benefits.
ありがとうございます。ありがとうございます。
Thank you very much. Thank you very much.
応募してくれた諸君のみんなもありがとうございましたー！
Thank you to everyone who applied!
そして次はなんだ？
And what's next?
オープン！来い来い来い！
Open! Come on, come on!
あ、来たー！じゃじゃーん！タワーコラボだ！
Oh, it's here! Tada! It's a Tower Collaboration!
これでタワーになるぞ！タワー！
We're gonna become a tower! Tower!
ということで、皆さん、タワーコラボ、もう情報公開されていますが、こちら！
So, everyone, the information for the Tower Collaboration is already out, but here it is!
全国4か所で行われる「holoX Tower Invasion」！イェーイ！
The 'holoX Tower Invasion' taking place at 4 locations nationwide! Yay!
12月4日から開催されます。
It starts on December 4th.
札幌テレビ塔、東京タワー、
Sapporo TV Tower, Tokyo Tower,
中部電力 MIRAI TOWER、梅田スカイビルで
Chubu Electric Power MIRAI TOWER, and Umeda Sky Building.
開催されますので、ぜひ皆さん行ってくださいね！
It'll be held there, so please go visit!
行ってね！イェーイ！
Go visit! Yay!
俺たちがholoX、10大タワーズ、タワー！
We are holoX, the 10 Great Towers, Tower!
おい待て待て！今回大事なことがあるんですけど、ちゃんと予約をしないとですね、
Hey, wait wait! There's something important: you have to book properly,
皆さん入れないんで、事前予約必須です！
otherwise you can't get in, so advance booking is mandatory!
そうなんだ！事前予約忘れてる人も多分いると思うので。
Is that so! I think some people might have forgotten to book in advance.
その場で行っても入れないらしいんで、ちゃんと予約を忘れるように！
Apparently you can't just walk in, so make sure not to forget to reserve!
ぜひぜひお願いしますよ！
We're counting on you!
はい！帰った帰った！お前の番だ！お前の番！
Yes! Go back, go back! It's your turn! Your turn!
次！オープン！
Next! Open!
はい！せーの！なんと、ホロライブの新サービス...
Yes! Ready, set... Believe it or not, a new Hololive service...
新しいサービス。ライブの感動を最速でその手に！
a new service. Get the excitement of the live concert in your hands as fast as possible!
おー！すごい！え、どういうこと？
Oh! Amazing! Eh, what does that mean?
秘密結社holoX、4周年のライブブロマイドが、
The Secret Society holoX 4th Anniversary Live Bromides...
なんと今日のライブの写真が明日からコンビニでプリントアウトできるんだ！
photos from today's live concert can be printed at convenience stores starting tomorrow!
えー！どこで手に入るんだ！
Eh! Where can we get them!?
対象店舗は、ファミリーマート、ローソン、ミニストップになります。
Target stores are FamilyMart, Lawson, and Ministop.
イェーイ！ありがとうございます！いっぱいある！どこでも！
Yay! Thank you! There are so many! Everywhere!
そして今からネットで事前購入ができるらしいです。
And apparently you can pre-order them online starting now.
マジで！？そうなの！？
Seriously!? Is that so!?
ただね、明日からコンビニでも写真を選びながら購入することもできるみたいなので、
However, you can also choose your photos and buy them at convenience stores from tomorrow,
詳しくは左下のリンクから確認してみてください。
so check the link at the bottom left for details.
こっちこっち！よしよしこっちこっち、この辺。
This way, this way! Right here, this way.
さらにですね、今回はそちらのお写真に、ブロマイドに私たちのメッセージをつけることができるみたいなんですけど。
Furthermore, this time it seems we can add messages to those photos, the bromides.
えー！いいことしかない！あ、来た来た来た。
Eh! Only good things! Oh, it's here, it's here.
今から書くそうです。
We're going to write them now.
えー！急すぎないか！ちょっと待って！浮いてる浮いてる。
Eh! Isn't that too sudden!? Wait a sec! They're floating!
しかも、何も考えてないけどまあまあまあ。
And I haven't thought of anything yet, but oh well.
何にどうなるこれ。考えて書いてください。はい！え、はい！
What... how will this turn out? Please think and write. Yes! Eh, yes!
時間も迫ってますからね、早く書いてください。ニャーニャーニャー。
Time is running out, so please write quickly. Nyan nyan nyan.
意外と集中力いるね、これ。つなげ！つなげ！安牌安牌で。
This requires more focus than I thought. Keep it going! Keep it going! Play it safe.
書けたー！早い！見せて！ちょっと待って！
Finished! Fast! Show me! Wait a sec!
これ、あ、かわいい。
This... oh, it's cute.
こよっぽいね。いつまで書いてんねん。
That's very Koyo-like. How long are you going to keep writing?
回収回収。出して、みんな。お願いしますね。ということでこれでお願いします。
Collect, collect. Everyone, show them. Please. So, please look forward to these.
まあ、みんな何書いたかすごく気になると思うのですが、こちらのメッセージの内容は、みんなが買ってからの...
Well, I'm sure everyone is curious about what we wrote, but the message content is for those who buy...
おーい！待て待て待て！ダメですよ！言わないで！
Hey! Wait wait wait! No! Don't say it!
みんな買ってからのお楽しみ！ダメですよ！ダメに決まってんだろ。
It's a surprise for those who buy them! No! Of course we can't show them yet.
あ、ごめんなさい、ごめんなさい。はい。
Oh, sorry, sorry. Yes.
はい。そして、まだ2枚あるんで、お次はこちら！オープン！
Yes. And we still have two left, so next is this! Open!
なんと、あの作品とコラボ！？
What, a collaboration with THAT work!?
えー！？何々！？あの作品？どれだ？どれだ？
Eh!? What is it!? That work? Which one? Which one?
ちょっと待て、これマジ知らない。あの作品ってなんですか？
Wait a sec, I really don't know this. What do you mean by 'that work'?
こちらをどうぞ。こちらをどうぞ。
Have a look at this. Have a look at this.
サテーー
Now then--
突然デハアルガ、
It is sudden,
或ル秘密結社ノ
but let's talk about
話ヲシヨウ。
a certain secret society.
人間ハ、
Humans are...
其ノ怪シイ集団ハ、
That mysterious group,
偶像ーー“アキドル”ナノダト云フ。
is said to be idols.
ソシテーー
And so—
正確ナ話ヲスルト、征服ショウトシテイルノハエデンノ星ラシイ。
To be precise, it seems they are trying to conquer the planet Eden.
タダ、ドイウコトカ、交ハルハズノナキ世界ガ、今回バカリハ油断シテシマッタラシイ。
However, for some reason, it seems the worlds that should never have crossed paths have let their guard down this once.
交 kou (2021)
Intersection (2021)
特別話 秘密結社holoX × 物語シリーズ 其ノ零
Special Story: Secret Society holoX x Monogatari Series Episode Zero
映像使用書体 HGP明朝B
Video Font: HGP Mincho B
〈物語〉シリーズ × holoX コラボ開催決定
Monogatari Series x holoX Collaboration Confirmed
うわあああああ！
Waaaah!
待って、やばい！いいの！？え、いいの！？
Wait, oh my god! Is this allowed?! Wait, really?!
え、まずい、やばい！
Wait, this is crazy, oh my god!
え、いいんですか！？
Wait, is this for real?!
え、やばすぎ、やばすぎ！え、めっちゃ大好きじゃんね！
Wait, this is too crazy, too crazy! We love it so much, don't we!
ね、好き！
Yeah, we love it!
え、やばすぎる！え、どういうこと！？
Wait, this is insane! Wait, what's happening?!
え、でもさ、どっか行っちゃった！どっか行っちゃったよ！
Wait, but they're gone! They disappeared!
え、ちょっと待って！ありがとうございます！
Wait, hold on a second! Thank you so much!
はい、ありがとうございます！
Yes, thank you very much!
なんと、マジで！え、怒られない？我輩。
Unbelievable, seriously! Wait, I'm not gonna get yelled at, am I?
怒られない、怒られない！
No one's gonna yell at you!
怒られるとしたら、台本を読んでないことで怒られる...
If anything, you'll get yelled at for not reading the script...
早く伝えようよ！なんと物語シリーズとのコラボが決定しました！
Let's just tell them quickly! A collaboration with the Monogatari series has been confirmed!
どういうこと！？どういうこと！？
What does this mean?! What's going on?!
どういうこと！ってみんなも言ってる！
Everyone's asking "What's going on!" too!
詳細は随時発表されるようなので、お楽しみに！
Details will be announced as they come, so stay tuned!
え、我々も分かっていない...
Wait, even we don't know...
そうなんです。本当に詳細が何も分かってない！
That's right. We literally know zero details!
どういうことですか！ええー！？
What do you mean by that?! What?!
どうなるんでしょうか...。いや、ちょっと我々も焦ってるんですけど...
I wonder what'll happen... Yeah, we're honestly a bit flustered ourselves...
え、いいんですか！？いいんですか！？っていう感じなんですけど...
Like, is this really okay?! Is it really okay?! That's how we feel...
最後に一つ、あるみたいなので、そちらに行きましょう！
But it looks like there's one last thing, so let's check it out!
あ、もう一個見ないといけないんだ！一旦、動揺を...
Oh, we have to see one more thing! Let's just calm down for a bit...
動揺を落ち着けてみんな！落ち着けて！
Everyone, calm your nerves! Just calm down!
俺たちが動揺してる間に、皆さんこの6つ目が何か...
While we're freaking out, everyone, try to guess what this 6th thing is...
コメントで教えてみてください！
Tell us in the comments!
何かなー？
I wonder what it is?
コメント見に行こう。やばかったね。
Let's look at the comments. That was crazy.
何かあるか？忍？忍かな？
Anything there? Shinobu? Could it be Shinobu?
怒られないかな？え、やば、何事！？何事ということですが！
Hope we don't get in trouble. Wait, crazy, what is it?! "What's going on" is right!
最後の一つは皆さん何だと思いますか？
What do you all think the final announcement is?
なんとですね、まあヒントを言うと、
Well, to give you a hint,
まあ今年、2曲作りましたよね？
well, we made two songs this year, right?
ああ、作った！いっぱい出た！
Oh, we did! So many came out!
全部でholoXって何曲ありますか？
How many songs does holoX have in total?
何曲？何曲だ？そして...
How many? I wonder how many? And...
あの、たくさん！
Um, a lot!
覚えてないのか！
You don't remember?!
holoXが出してきた企画を除きまして、全部で...
Excluding the ones for special projects, holoX has...
7曲あります！なんと7曲！すごーい！多いね！
7 songs in total! A whole 7 songs! Wow! Amazing! That's a lot!
え、ってことは？もしや？
Wait, which means? Could it be?
え、みんな分かってる？みんなコメント欄分かってきたんじゃない？
Wait, does everyone know? Is the comment section starting to figure it out?
どうだ？あ、来てる来てる来てる！
How is it? Oh, they're getting it, they're getting it!
ということで、気づいてる人もいるみたいなので、
So, since it looks like some of you have noticed,
やっぱりあちらでございます！6枚目オープン！
it's exactly what you think! Open the 6th panel!
バーン！じゃん！なんと！
BAM! Tada! Unbelievable!
Secret Society holoX 1st Album "Secret ORDER" 2026.04.08 RELEASE
ファーストアルバムが出ます！
Our 1st album is coming out!
やったあああああ！うれしいい！
Yaaaay! I'm so happy!
うれしい！ということで！
I'm so glad! So!
ファーストアルバム、ファーストオーダーじゃない、
The 1st album, it's not First Order,
ファーストアルバム、シークレットオーダー！
the 1st album is "Secret ORDER"!
混ざった混ざった！大丈夫大丈夫。シークレットオーダーだよ。しょうがないよ。
You got them mixed up! It's okay. It's Secret ORDER. Totally understandable.
はい、こちらのシークレットオーダー、holoXでの4年間をギュッと詰め込んだアルバムとなっております！
Yes, this Secret ORDER is an album packed with our four years together as holoX!
我々のデビュー曲「ジョヤリペイント」はオリジナルバージョンに加えて、
In addition to the original version of our debut song "Joyful Paint,"
本策のために新たにリアレンジされたバージョンも収録されています！
it also includes a newly re-arranged version just for this release!
何ですってー！
What was that?!
そしてさらに、なんかまだ未発表の楽曲も...
And what's more, there are some still unannounced songs too...
え？じゃあ、7、8、9、10、11...
Wait, so 7, 8, 9, 10, 11...
多すぎる多すぎる！わらわらわら。
Too many, too many! Whoa, whoa, whoa.
ということでですね、通常版になるんですけど...
So, this is regarding the regular edition...
あ、ちょっと、上が見えないです。早い早い。
Oh, wait, I can't see the top. Too fast, too fast.
流れがね。早いですね。すみません。
The flow, yeah. It's moving fast. Sorry about that.
通常版には初回限定特典があります！ありますよ！
The regular edition comes with a first-press limited bonus! It sure does!
こちらでございますね。各メンバーのソロバージョン、
This is it right here. Solo versions for each member,
そしてジャケット4種類のうち、ランダムで1枚つきます！
and you'll get one of four different jackets at random!
そしてこちらですね。4枚並べると...
And also, if you line up all four...
どうやら一枚絵になるとのことですよ！
apparently, they form a single large illustration!
え、すごい！つながりそうな顔してる！ラプちゃんの角が刀の上に...
Whoa, amazing! They definitely look like they'd connect! La+-chan's horn is above the sword...
あ、本当だ！本当だ！じゃあこれさ、並べないと...
Oh, you're right! You're right! Then we definitely have to line them up...
並べないとね。並べないと。そして...
Gotta line them up. Absolutely. And...
完全生産限定版封入特典は、
The bonuses included in the complete limited production edition are,
カッコよさ満点の今回のアルバムには、
for this incredibly cool album,
holoXらしい秘密の仕掛けが！
a secret gimmick worthy of holoX!
秘密の仕掛け！？え、我々も分かってないぞ...
A secret gimmick?! Wait, we don't even know what that is...
隠されているとか！
Like something hidden?!
な、なんですって！？ちょっと私達も分からないのですが...
W-What was that?! Honestly, even we're in the dark here...
この後22時から販売開始です！
Sales start right after this at 10 PM!
ぜひぜひご予約お願いいたします！お願いします！
Please, please do pre-order! We're counting on you!
ということで、めっちゃ告知盛りだくさんだったんですけど、
So, we had a ton of announcements today,
まあね、この告知カードちゃんたちは、これで役目も終わりということで、
but well, these announcement cards have served their purpose now,
消えろー！バイバーイ！
Disappear! Bye-bye!
それで消せんの！？コヨー！いやここ流石に金かけすぎだろ！
You can make them disappear like that?! Koyo! Seriously, they spent way too much money on this!
何だこれ！このギミックやばいだろ！
What the heck! This gimmick is insane!
一瞬だけね！一瞬だけ。こよの力ってすげーからな、みんな！
Just for a second! Just a second. Koyo's power is amazing, you guys!
はい、ということで、ライブもラストスパートでございます！
Alright, so the live show is entering its last spurt!
この後ですね、何やらちょっとお知らせ？サプライズ？があるらしいですよ！
Apparently, there's some kind of announcement? Or surprise? coming up later!
なになに！？
What is it?!
はい、最後までチャンネルはそのままでお願いいたします！
Yes, please stay tuned to this channel until the very end!
お願いしまーす！
Please do!
いくぞみんな、最後まで！
Let's go everyone, until the end!
楽しんで、いくぞー！
Have fun! Here we go!
いくぞー！イエーイ！
Let's go! Yay!
そこに跪け！
Kneel before me!
一刀両断叩き切れ！
Cut them down with a single stroke!
終わりなき輪廻に迷いし孤狼よ
O lone wolf wandering in the endless cycle of rebirth.
漆黒の翼で誘おう
I shall invite you with jet-black wings.
我ら、エデンの星を統べる者
We are those who rule the star of Eden.
秘密結社...
Secret Society...
holoX!
でござる！
I am!
Woah oh Woah oh oh oh...
あんなのどうしようもないこの世界
There's nothing to be done about that world.
壊してほしい？
Do you want me to break it?
嗚呼、終末告げる鐘が鳴る
Ah, the bell announcing the end is tolling.
Woah pop-a-da-low Let's sing a song of ink and you can also sing along
心地いいことだけがすべて
Pleasant things are everything.
落ちていく闇の底へ
Falling to the bottom of the darkness.
M-A-M-A-M-A Melody
ほらどうぞどうぞ手の鳴る方へ
Come now, come towards the sound of the clapping hands.
もう逃げられやしない
There's no escaping now.
ほら 闇に染まれば
Look, if you're stained in darkness...
世界を塗り替えろ
Repaint the world!
望めばくれてやろう すべて
I'll give it all to you if you wish.
常識 破り捨てろ
Tear away common sense.
くるくる狂い倒せ 火をつけろ
Go mad and spin around, set it on fire!
Woah-pa-pa-da-pa
すべてを喰らい尽くせ
Devour everything.
Woah-pa-pa-da-pa
機密を教えてやろう
I'll teach you the secret.
Woah oh Woah oh oh oh...
悪のカリスマ 導くぞため息さ
The charisma of evil, I'll lead you, it's a sigh.
正義とか知らないし地ならしして誘い
I don't know about justice, I'll level the ground and invite you.
不真面目に不真面目 礼賛の通過儀礼
Unserious and unserious, a rite of passage for praise.
望み求め願い叶え 世界征服
Seeking desires, fulfilling wishes, world conquest.
Wa-pa-pa-da-low Let's sing a song of...
退屈な世界へ バイバイバイ
To the boring world, bye-bye-bye.
冷めることのない夢を見せる
I'll show you a dream that never cools down.
ほら お眠りなさい
Now, please go to sleep.
もっと もっと 遠くへ
Further, even further...
ほらどうぞどうぞ行きたいでしょう？
Come on, you want to go, don't you?
もうやめられやしない
You can't stop anymore.
ほら 悪に染まれば
Look, if you're stained with evil...
世界を塗り替えろ
Repaint the world!
望むもの与えよう すべて
I'll give you what you desire.
ルールを書き換えろ
Rewrite all the rules.
くるくる回し尽くせ 火をつけろ
Spin it all around, set it on fire!
Woah-pa-pa-da-pa
すべてをまがいものへ
Turn everything into fakes.
Woah-pa-pa-da-pa
機密を教えてやろう
I'll teach you the secret.
ついに4周年
Finally, the 4th anniversary.
狂気の宴の始まりだ
The banquet of madness begins.
貴様ら 準備はいいか！
Are you bastards ready?!
括目せよ！
Witness this!
holoX! holoX!
手を上げろ！ 手を上げろ！
Hands up! Hands up!
いろは！ いろは！
Iroha! Iroha!
叫ぶでござる！
I'm shouting!
こより！ こより！
Koyori! Koyori!
踊れ！ 踊れ！
Dance! Dance!
世界を秘密でholoX！ 世界を変えてくholoX！
The world in secrets, holoX! Changing the world, holoX!
ルイねぇ！ ルイねぇ！ もっと！ もっと！
Lui-nee! Lui-nee! More! More!
ラプラス！ ラプラス！ 最後は全員で！
Laplace! Laplace! Finally, everyone together!
holoX! holoX!
世界を秘密でholoX!
The world in secrets, holoX!
世界を変えてくholoX!
Changing the world, holoX!
世界をこの手にholoX!
The world in our hands, holoX!
心を解き放て
Set your heart free.
ほらどうぞどうぞ身をまかせて
Come on, just entrust yourself.
もう逃げられやしない
There's no escaping now.
ほら 闇に染まれば
Look, if you're stained in darkness...
世界を塗り替えろ
Repaint the world!
望めばくれてやろう すべて
I'll give it all to you if you wish.
常識 破り捨てろ
Tear away common sense.
くるくる狂い倒せ 火をつけろ
Go mad and spin around, set it on fire!
Woah-pa-pa-da-pa
すべてを喰らい尽くせ
Devour everything.
Woah-pa-pa-da-pa
機密を教えてやろう
I'll teach you the secret.
Woah oh Woah oh oh oh...
我らエデンの星を統べる者、秘密結社...
We who rule the planet Eden, Secret Society...
holoX！
holoX!
Yes My Dark!!
機は熟した。
The time is ripe.
永劫より現れし英霊たちよ、
O heroic spirits appearing from eternity,
準備はいいか！
Are you ready!
あ〜〜！！！
Aaaaah!!!
Are you ready?
ラッパッパ LaPaLaPa ラッパッパ LaPaLaPa ラッパッパ
Rappa-ppa LaPaLaPa Rappa-ppa LaPaLaPa Rappa-ppa
夜が深まる ほらダークネス
Night deepens, behold, darkness
能ある鷹はPONで隠そう
A clever hawk hides behind clumsiness
本能に従え エゴイスティック
Follow your instincts, egoistic
のっとにんにん!! サムライGIRL
Not nin-nin!! Samurai GIRL
闇金しないけど フルベッドでしょ シャキシャキ
No loan sharking here, but it's a full bet, right? Snip snip
征服すればOK 切り裂く赤字 ジャキンジャキン
It's OK if we conquer, slashing through the deficit, Clang clang
悪の手のひら 踊りたくなる
The palm of evil makes me want to dance
ほら君 気付けば ノリノリです
See, before you know it, you're in the groove
どうしようもない Don't show, No mind
It can't be helped, Don't show, No mind
堕ちてく運命
Falling destiny
ならしょうがない もう全部
Then it can't be helped, everything now
塗り替えよう
Let's repaint it all
エクスとエクスとエクスが
Ex and Ex and Ex
交差する真ん中で
Intersect in the center
ネクストネクストネクスト
Next next next
世界はもう始まってる
The world has already begun
Wow oh oh...
飛びな飛びな 闇が呼ぶ方へ
Fly away, fly away, to where the darkness calls
Wow oh oh...
暗黒のエクスデス
Darkness Ex-deadly
混沌としたこの世界を我らholoX色に塗り替えるのだ！
We shall repaint this chaotic world in the colors of holoX!
皆の者、かかれ！
Everyone, attack!
Yes My Dark!!!
完全漆黒（アブソリュート・ダークネス・インフィニティ）！
Absolute Darkness Infinity!
エデンの星は我が手中に！
The planet Eden is in my hands!
魔眼ホークアイ！
Evil Eye Hawk-Eye!
お前もholoXの一員となるのだ！
You too shall become a member of holoX!
カヤリニュウム・バ〜〜ン！
Koyalinium Burn!
これで君も、こよりメイトだ！
With this, you are also a Koyori-mate!
疾風木ノ葉斬り！一刀両断、叩き斬れ！
Hurricane Leaf Slash! One stroke, cut them down!
トカゲの軍勢を断つ！
I'll sever the lizard army!
どうしようもない Don't show, No mind
It can't be helped, Don't show, No mind
堕ちてく運命
Falling destiny
ならしょうがない もう全部
Then it can't be helped, everything now
塗り替えよう
Let's repaint it all
刮目せよ！！
Behold!!
エクスとエクスとエクスが
Ex and Ex and Ex
交差する真ん中で
Intersect in the center
ネクストネクストネクスト
Next next next
世界はもう始まってる
The world has already begun
Wow oh oh...
飛びな飛びな 夢見る方へ
Fly away, fly away, to where dreams lead
Wow oh oh...
笑うのは holoXです
The ones laughing will be holoX
ラッパッパ LaPaLaPa ラッパッパ LaPaLaPa ラッパッパ
Rappa-ppa LaPaLaPa Rappa-ppa LaPaLaPa Rappa-ppa
イェ〜〜〜〜イ！！！
Yaaaaay!!!
機ハ熟シタ
The time is ripe
全テノ "holoxer" ヘ告グ
Notice to all "holoxers"
集ヘ、決戦ノ地ヘ
Gather at the final battleground
2026.4.29
PIA ARENA MM
秘密結社holoX Live 2026 MISSION [ファーストミッション]
Secret Society holoX Live 2026 MISSION [First Mission]
世界ヲ手ニスル 準備ハイイカ
Are you ready to take over the world?
狂気ノ宴ノハジマリダ
The banquet of madness begins
#SSholoX世界リペイント計画
#SSholoXWorldRepaintProject
やったーー！！！やったーー！！！
We did it!!! We did it!!!
みんな驚いてくれてる！
Everyone is surprised!
いかがでしたか？
How was it?
やばいね、やばいね。
It's amazing, isn't it?
ということで、なんと我々の現地ライブが決まりました！
So, our local live concert has been decided!
やったーー！！！
Yaaaay!!!
ありがとうございます！
Thank you so much!
ファーストミッション、ぴあアリーナMM！
First Mission at Pia Arena MM!
ということで、みんなそれぞれ感想とライブへの抱負をお願いします！
So, let's hear everyone's thoughts and enthusiasm for the live!
まずは、じゃあ私から。
First, well, starting with me.
決まったなぁ！
It's finally decided!
いやめちゃくちゃね、あの、デビューの時からライブやりたいねって言ってて。
Well, we've been saying we want to do a live since our debut.
デビュー前から！
Even before our debut!
それがもうありがたいことに...
And now, thankfully...
みんなの協力のおかげで、ホロクサーさんたちの応援のおかげで、
Thanks to everyone's cooperation and the support of the Holoxers...
叶いました！やったー！
It's come true! Yay!
やったー！
Yay!
ありがとうございます。
Thank you very much.
もう、holoXのみんなで当日盛り上げたいと思いますので、
All of us in holoX want to liven things up on that day...
ぜひみんな遊びに来てください！
So please come and hang out with us!
かっこいいholoXを見に来てね！
Come see the cool holoX!
ということで、続いては、じゃあこよ！
So, next up is, well, Koyo!
はい！えー、ま、今言ってた通り、みんなライブやりたいねって話もしてたし、
Yes! Well, as she just said, we were all talking about wanting to do a live,
やっぱこよは一番忘れられない風景が、
And for Koyo, the most unforgettable scenery...
初めてのフェスでholoXでやった時の、あのジョーリペイントで会場がもうわーっとなってくれたのを浴びた時。
...was when we performed as holoX at our first Fes and felt the crowd roar during "Jouri Paint".
あれをもうずっと忘れられないんで、
I can never forget that sensation,
やっぱり、その、今度はね、ホロクサーさんたちだけの会場、俺たちの箱で、
So, now we get to do it in a venue with only Holoxers, at our own place,
やれるわけじゃないですか。
We can do it, can't we?
そうだね。
That's right.
俺たちの箱で！
At our own place!
めちゃくちゃ嬉しいです。
I'm so happy.
そしてできて、本当に、この、やらせてくれることに、してくれた大人の皆さんにも、
And I'm also really thankful to all the staff who made this possible.
大人の皆さん！
Staff members!
ありがとうございます。
Thank you very much.
で、この4人のできる力を全て出して、そして歌とダンスもね、
So, we'll put out everything the four of us can do, and as for singing and dancing,
より一層力を込めてやっていきますので、
We'll be putting even more heart into it.
絶対現地、そして現地来れない人は映像でも絶対見に来てください！
Please come to the venue, or watch the stream! Please see us!
よろしくお願いします！
We look forward to it!
みんな！生でござるたちの声が聴ける機会、
Everyone! An opportunity to hear our voices live,
holoXのこのハーモニーが聴ける機会！
An opportunity to hear this holoX harmony!
ハーモニー！
Harmony!
掛け声！俺たちの、共鳴！
Our shout! Our resonance!
共鳴が聴ける機会、来たぞー！
The chance to hear our resonance has come!
いやもう本当にね、holoX、やっぱみんな言ってるけどデビュー前からね、
Well, really, like everyone's saying, since before our debut,
このメンバーでやりたいってずっと言っていたので、
We've been saying we want to do this with these members,
それがやっと叶ってね、デカい声出して、みんなで盛り上がれるのを今か今かと楽しみに致しております！
And that's finally come true, so I'm really looking forward to shouting and getting hyped with everyone!
我々もね、4人とも、しっかり当日までレッスンや、練習も含めパフォーマンスも全部、色々みんなに楽しんでもらえることいっぱい考えて挑みますので、
The four of us will also be working hard on lessons, practice, and planning various things for everyone to enjoy until that day,
見ている皆さんもぜひ、全力で楽しみにして、そして当日は楽しんでください！
So everyone watching, please look forward to it and enjoy the day!
頑張ります！盛り上げる準備できてます！
We'll do our best! We're ready to hype it up!
頑張るぞー！
Let's go!
じゃあ最後、総帥、決めてくれ！
Now finally, Leader, wrap it up!
いやちょ、毎回この最後やめてほしいんだよね、しんどいよ。
Wait, I wish you'd stop making me the last one every time, it's tough.
ちょっとみんな、ついにholoXが、俺たちが、ライブ！
Wait everyone, finally holoX, we are... doing a LIVE!
もうみんなはさ、もうすごいライブやりたい、音楽大好きみたいな、ずっと聴いてたからさ、
I've always heard you all talking about wanting to do a live and how much you love music,
俺は嬉しいよ。
So I'm happy for you.
当事者よ！
You're one of us!
私もっす。やっぱりライブがね、一番楽しいから。
Me too. Well, a live is the most fun, after all.
やっぱholoXの活動ってなんかライブって感じじゃん。
HoloX's activities feel like a "live" thing, you know.
だからそれがさ、俺たちだけで、しかもホロクサーがばーっているところでできるのが嬉しいよな。
So I'm happy we can do that by ourselves, with Holoxers all over the place.
熱いや。
That's hot.
俺たち本当に色々あったけど、これからも本当に4人いれば大丈夫だから。頑張ろう。
We've been through a lot, but as long as we have the four of us, it'll be fine. Let's do our best.
頑張ろう！一致団結していこう。
Let's do our best! Let's stay united.
頑張るぞー！
Let's go!
速報です！トレンド1位ということで！
Breaking news! We're trending #1!
ありがとうございます！
Thank you very much!
ここから4月29日まで、もう止まらねえぞで、マインドに入れまくっててください。
From now until April 29th, keep the "We're not stopping" mindset!
はいということで改めて、秘密結社holoX 1st LIVE 「First Mission」は4月29日、ぴあアリーナMMにて開催されます！
So once again, Secret Society holoX 1st LIVE "First Mission" will be held on April 29th at Pia Arena MM!
Secret Society holoX 1st LIVE 2026
Mission ファーストミッション
2026.4.29 Wed. PIA ARENA MM
Secret Society holoX 1st LIVE 2026
Mission First Mission
2026.4.29 Wed. PIA ARENA MM
開けとけ、開けとけ！
Save the date!
諸々の詳細は後日発表予定とのことなので、皆さん続報を待たれよでござる！
Details will be announced at a later date, so please wait for further news!
そして、先ほど聴いていただきました新曲「響宴エクスデス」、この後配信もありますので！
And, you just heard our new song "Kyouen Ex-Death", and it'll be available for streaming later!
22時10分よりですね、
Starting at 10:10 PM,
MVをプレミア公開したいと思いまーす！
we'll be having an MV premiere!
イエーイ！おー！
Yay! Ohhh!
このあと MVプレミア公開
MV Premiere Coming Up Next
おしゃれですね、かっこいい！
It's so stylish! So cool!
そして、本日24時ですね、
And today at midnight,
12月2日の0時に
at 0:00 AM on December 2nd,
デジタルリリースが開始されますので、
the digital release will begin!
ライブに向けて、たくさん聴いてくれよな！
So listen to it a lot for the live!
や、もうコールできるところいっぱいだからね！
Yeah, there are so many parts to call out to!
めちゃめちゃ、もうライブのための曲だから！
Seriously, this song was made for the live!
エクステ！エクステ！エクステ！
Exte! Exte! Exte!
お前ら新曲いっぱい聴いて、
You guys listen to the new song a lot,
予習して、ライブ楽しみにして待っててほしい！
study up, and look forward to the live!
そしてアルバム『シークレットオーダー』を持って...
And bring our album, 'Secret Order'...
持って？持って？持って？
Bring it? Bring it? Bring it?
奪われないように気をつけてね！持ってね！
Be careful it doesn't get stolen! Bring it!
ライブ来てね！運ばなきゃ！
Come to the live! We gotta carry it!
オッケー！聴いて予習してね！
Okay! Listen and study up!
アルバムは、えっと、22時から販売開始！
The album starts selling at, uh, 10:00 PM!
もう一分もない！早い！
Not even a minute left! So fast!
みんな買ってね！
Everyone, please buy it!
ホロックスのみんな！
HoloX fans!
え、本当に4年間ありがとう！
Um, really, thank you for these 4 years!
付いてきてくれてありがとう！
Thank you for following us!
来年はもうホロックスの、
Next year will be
我々の年にしていくので、頑張ろうね！
HoloX's year, our year, so let's do our best!
5年目もよろしくお願いしますね！
Please support us in our 5th year too!
よろしくお願いします！！
We look forward to it!!
じゃあみんな、せーのでいくよ！うん！
Alright everyone, on three! Yeah!
せーの、バイバイー！
Ready, bye-bye!
解釈！解釈！解釈！
Kaishaku! Kaishaku! Kaishaku!
やったー！やったー！やったー！
We did it! We did it! We did it!
4周年をお祝いしてくれてありがとうございました！！これからもholoXをよろしくお願いします♡
Thank you for celebrating our 4th anniversary!! Please continue to support holoX♡